<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>kaudiocreator.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2+</project_license>
  <name>KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">К‑аудио-стваралац</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑audio-stvaralac</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑аудио-стваралац</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑audio-stvaralac</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kaudiocreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KAudioCreator</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKAudioCreatorxx</name>
  <summary>CD Ripper</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bs">CD čupač</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Extractor de CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">CD extraktor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Cd-Ripper</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">CD-Ripper</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Αντιγραφέας CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">CD Ripper</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Ripeador de CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Copiador de CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Estrattore di CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">CD 추출기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">CD-ripper</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Program zgrywający CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Extracção de CD's</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Extrator de CD</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">CD riper</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Zajemalnik CD-jev</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr">Чупач ЦД‑ова</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-Latn">Čupač CD‑ova</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Чупач ЦД‑ова</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Čupač CD‑ova</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Cd-lagring</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для видобування даних КД</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxCD Ripperxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KAudioCreator is an audio CD ripper, which uses "cdparanoia" as a backend to extract the tracks
      and later it encodes them to mp3 or ogg files (or many other formats supported)
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">KAudioCreator je  audio CD ekstraktor, koji koristi "cdparanoia" kao pozadinu za vađenje traka i kasnije ih kodira u  mp3 ili ogg datoteke (ili mnoge druge podržane formate)</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KAudioCreator és un extractor d'àudio de CD, que utilitza el «cdparanoia» com a dorsal per extreure les peces i codificar-les més tard a fitxers mp3 o ogg (o molts altres formats acceptats)</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">KAudioCreator er en lyd-cd-ripper, der bruger "cdparanoia" som backend til at udtrække sporene og derefter indkoder dem som mp3- eller ogg-filer (eller mange andre understøttede formater)</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το KAudioCreator είναι ένας αντιγραφέςα CD, που χρησιμοποιεί το "cdparanoia" ως σύστημα υποστήριξης για την εξαγωγή κομματιών και έπειτα τα κωδικοποιεί σε αρχεία mp3 ή ogg (ή σε πολλούς άλλους υποστηριζόμενους τύπους κωδικοποίησης)</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KAudioCreator is an audio CD ripper, which uses "cdparanoia" as a backend to extract the tracks and later it encodes them to mp3 or ogg files (or many other formats supported)</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KAudioCreator es un ripeador de CD de audio que usa «cdparanoia» como motor para extraer las pistas y codificarlas a continuación en archivos mp3 u ogg (u otros formatos implementados)</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KAudioCreator é un copiador de CD que usa «cdparanoia» como motor para extraer as pistas, que posteriormente codifica como ficheiros MP3 ou OGG (ou outro dos moitos formatos que ofrece).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KAudioCreator è un estrattore di CD audio, che utilizza «cdparanoia» come motore per estrarre le tracce e successivamente le codifica in file mp3 o ogg (o molti altri formati supportati)</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KAudioCreator는 "cdparanoia"를 백엔드로 사용하고 MP3, OGG(외 여러 형식 지원) 등으로 인코딩할 수 있는 오디오 CD 추출기입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KAudioCreator is een audio-cd-ripper, die "cdparanoia" als backend gebruikt om de tracks uit te pakken en later deze te coderen naar mp3 of ogg-bestanden (of vele andere ondersteunde formaten)</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KAudioCreator jest programem do zgrywania płyt CD, który używa "cdparanoia" jako silnika do wydobywania utworów i późniejszego kodowania ich do plików mp3 lub ogg (lub wielu innych obsługiwanych formatów)</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KAudioCreator é um programação de extracção do áudio de CD's, que usa o "cdparanoia" como infra-estrutura para extrair as faixas e que as codifica mais tarde como ficheiros MP3 ou OGG (ou em outros formatos suportados)</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">KAudioCreator é um programa para extração do áudio de CDs, que usa o "cdparanoia" como infraestrutura para extrair as faixas e depois as converte em arquivos MP3 ou OGG (ou vários outros formatos suportados)</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KAudioCreator je audio CD riper, ktorý používa backend cdparanoia na extrahovanie stôp a neskôr ich kóduje do mp3 alebo ogg súborov (sú podporované aj mnohé iné formáty)</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KAudioCreator je zajemalnik zvočnih CD-jev, ki kot zaledni program za razširjanje skladb uporablja program "cdparanoia". Razširjene skladbe lahko kodira v datoteke mp3, ogg ali katero drugo podprto vrsto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">К‑аудио-стваралац је чупач ЦД‑ова, који користи наредбу <command>cdparanoia</command> као позадину за извлачење нумера. Потом их кодира у МП3 или ОГГ фајлове (или у неки други од многих подржаних формата).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">K‑audio-stvaralac je čupač CD‑ova, koji koristi naredbu <command>cdparanoia</command> kao pozadinu za izvlačenje numera. Potom ih kodira u MP3 ili OGG fajlove (ili u neki drugi od mnogih podržanih formata).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">К‑аудио-стваралац је чупач ЦД‑ова, који користи наредбу <command>cdparanoia</command> као позадину за извлачење нумера. Потом их кодира у МП3 или ОГГ фајлове (или у неки други од многих подржаних формата).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">K‑audio-stvaralac je čupač CD‑ova, koji koristi naredbu <command>cdparanoia</command> kao pozadinu za izvlačenje numera. Potom ih kodira u MP3 ili OGG fajlove (ili u neki drugi od mnogih podržanih formata).</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kaudiocreator är ett verktyg för lagring av ljud-cd, som använder "cdparanoia" som gränssnitt för att extrahera spår, och senare kodar dem till MP3- eller OGG-filer (eller många andra format som stöds).</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KAudioCreator — програма для видобування цифрових даних з компакт-дисків, у якій для отримання даних композицій використано програму «cdparanoia». Ця програма здатна виконати кодування отриманих даних до файлів mp3 чи ogg. Крім того, передбачено підтримку і багатьох інших форматі.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKAudioCreator is an audio CD ripper, which uses "cdparanoia" as a backend to extract the tracks and later it encodes them to mp3 or ogg files (or many other formats supported)xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="bs">Svojstva:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-Latn">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Могућности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Mogućnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>CDDB lookup to extract the album and track information</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">CDDB pregled za ekstrakciju informacija o albumu i traci</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cerca CDDB per extreure la informació de l'àlbum i la peça</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">CDDB-opslag til at udtrække informationer om albummer og sange</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αναζήτηση σε CDDB για την εξαγωγή πληροφοριών για το άλμπουμ και το κομμάτι</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">CDDB lookup to extract the album and track information</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Búsqueda CDDB para extraer información sobre el álbum y las pistas</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Consultas en CDDB para obter información das pistas e do álbum.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ricerca CDDB per estrarre le informazioni sull'album e sulla traccia</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">앨범과 트랙 정보를 CDDB에서 검색</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">CDDB-lookup om de informatie over album en track op te halen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie w CDDB do wydobywania szczegółów o utworze i albumie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pesquisa no CDDB para extrair a informação do álbum e das faixas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquisa no CDDB para extrair as informações do álbum e das faixas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Vyhľadávanie v CDDB na extrahovanie informácií o albume a stope</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Poizvedbe CDDB za pridobivanje podrobnosti o albumu in skladbi</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Потрага на ЦДДБ‑у за извлачење података о албуму и нумерама.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Potraga na CDDB‑u za izvlačenje podataka o albumu i numerama.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Потрага на ЦДДБ‑у за извлачење података о албуму и нумерама.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Potraga na CDDB‑u za izvlačenje podataka o albumu i numerama.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">CDDB-uppslagning för att extrahera album- och spårinformation</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Пошук у CDDB для отримання даних щодо альбому і композиції.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCDDB lookup to extract the album and track informationxx</li>
      <li>Different encoding formats supported (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Podržani razni formati kodiranja (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Hi ha implementats formats de codificació diferents (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Forskellige indkodningsformater understøttes (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Υποστηρίζονται διάφοροι τύποι κωδικοποίησης (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Different encoding formats supported (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite usar diferentes formatos de codificación (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Ofrece varios formatos de codificación (OGG, MP3, FLAC).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Diversi formati di codifica supportati (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 인코딩 지원(OGG, MP3, FLAC)</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verschillende ondersteunde coderingsformaten (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługa wielu formatów kodowania (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diversos formatos de codificação suportados (OGG, MP3, FLAC)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para diversos formatos de codificação (OGG, MP3, FLAC)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rôzne formáty kódovania podporované (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Več podprtih vrst za kodiranje (ogg, mp3, flac)</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Подршка за различите формате кодирања (ОГГ, МП3, ФЛАЦ).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Podrška za različite formate kodiranja (OGG, MP3, FLAC).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Подршка за различите формате кодирања (ОГГ, МП3, ФЛАЦ).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Podrška za različite formate kodiranja (OGG, MP3, FLAC).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Olika kodningsformat stöds (OGG, MP3, FLAC)</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка різних форматів кодування даних (ogg, mp3, flac).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDifferent encoding formats supported (ogg, mp3, flac)xx</li>
      <li>Different filename formats using tags</li>
      <li xml:lang="bs">Razni formati imena datoteka koristeći oznake</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Formats diferents de nom de fitxer usant etiquetes</li>
      <li xml:lang="da">Forskellige filnavneformater med brug af mærker</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Διάφοροι τύποι κωδικοποίησης με χρήση ετικετών</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Different filename formats using tags</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Diferentes formatos de nombres de archivos usando etiquetas</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite distintos formatos para o nome dos ficheiros mediante etiquetas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Diversi formati dei nomi dei file che utilizzano i tag</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">태그에서 파일 이름 변경 지원</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verschillende formaten bestandsnamen door tags te gebruiken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Znaczniki dla różnych formatów plików </li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diferentes formatos de nomes de ficheiros, usando as marcas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Usa etiquetas para diferentes formatos de nomes dos arquivos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rôzne formáty názvov súborov pomocou značiek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Raznolike oblike imen datotek z uporabo oznak</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr">Разноврсни формати имена фајла на основу ознака.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-Latn">Raznovrsni formati imena fajla na osnovu oznaka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavian">Разноврсни формати имена фајла на основу ознака.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sr-ijekavianlatin">Raznovrsni formati imena fajla na osnovu oznaka.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Olika filnamnsformat med användning av taggar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка створення різних назв файлів на основі міток композицій.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxDifferent filename formats using tagsxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kaudiocreator</url>
  <url type="help">http://docs.kde.org/development/en/extragear-multimedia/kaudiocreator/index.html</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kaudiocreator.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kaudiocreator</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
